<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Properties version="1.0" language="en" country="US" lookandfeel="NORMAL" xmlns:xsi=“http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance” xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation=“”>
<String id="LOCALE">Spanish_Spain</String>

<!-- Framework Strings -->
    <String id="DIALOG_BUTTON_YES">YES</String>
    <String id="DIALOG_BUTTON_NO">NO</String>
	<String id="DIALOG_BUTTON_OK">OK</String>
    <String id="DIALOG_BUTTON_CANCEL">CANCEL</String>

	<String id="UNEXPECTED_ERROR">An unexpected error has occurred!  By clicking “Send Report,” you will send us debugging information that may help us fix the problem in the future.&cr;&cr;You can also contact us directly by sending an email to feedback@popcap.com.</String>

	<String id="PLEASE_HELP">Please provide us with as much information as you can about this error. Is this the first time it has occurred? Have you played other PopCap Deluxe games without any problems? Have you recently updated your computer drivers or other software that may be interfering with this program?</String>

	<String id="FAILED_CONNECT_POPCAP">Unable to connect to PopCap servers. Please check your Internet connection.&cr;If you have a dial-up connection, you may need to manually connect to your Internet service provider.</String>

	<String id="HARDWARE_ACCEL_SWITCHED_ON">3D acceleration has been enabled for this session.&cr;If this causes the game to run slower, you should disable it.&cr;Do you want to keep 3D acceleration enabled?</String>

	<String id="HARDWARE_ACCEL_CONFIRMATION">3D acceleration confirmation</String>

	<String id="HARDWARE_ACCEL_NOT_WORKING">3D acceleration may not have worked correctly in this session.&cr;If you notice problems with the graphics, you may need to disable 3D acceleration.&cr;Do you want to keep 3D acceleration enabled?</String>

	<String id="FATAL_ERROR">FATAL ERROR</String>

    <String id="PLEASE_SET_COLOR_DEPTH">Please change your desktop color depth to 16 bits.</String>

	<String id="FAILED_INIT_DIRECTDRAW">DirectDraw could not be initialized:&nbsp;</String>

	<String id="UNABLE_OPEN_PROPERTIES">Unable to open properties file&nbsp;</String>

	<String id="PROPERTIES_SIG_FAILED">An error occurred while checking the signature. </String>

    <String id="INVALID_COMMANDLINE_PARAM">Invalid command line parameter:</String> 

	<String id="APP_REQUIRES_DIRECTX">This application requires DirectX to run.  You can download DirectX from http://www.microsoft.com/directx</String>
    <String id="YOU_NEED_DIRECTX">You need DirectX</String>

</Properties>
